MAYUR WAGHMODE

DevOps Engineer

My Contact

waghmodemayur17@gmail.com

(+91 72496 69807

Pune, Maharshtra

<u>LinkedIn</u>

My Blogs

GitHub

Skills

- **DevOps Tools**: Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Terraform, Ansible, Git, GitOps
- CI/CD: GitHub Actions, Tekton pipelines, Jenkins, CircleCl, Travis Cl
- Cloud: AWS, IBM Cloud, Microsoft Azure
- **Programming Languages**: Python, Golang, Core Java, C++, C, Linux, Bash
- Frameworks: Spring Boot, Android, Flask

Certifications

- Certified Kubernetes Administrator
- Azure Fundamentals(AZ-900)
- GitOps Fundamentals

Achievements

- Persistent Bravo Individual Award (May 2022)
- Persistent Ace Individual Award (Feb. 2022)

Other Details

- **Soft Skills**: Team Player, Communication, Leadership, Optimistic
- Languages Known: English, Hindi, Marathi
- Hobbies: Playing Chess, Reading blogs

About Me

2+ Years of experience in DevOps

Experienced in using container and container orchestration tools – **Docker, Podman, Buildah, Kubernetes, Openshift**Proficient in writing **CICD** workflows for different solutions
Building and testing **open-source** software, interacting with and contributing to open-source communities **Certified Kubernetes Administrator** from Linux Foundation **Quick learner** in adapting new skills, **effective communication**, and **time management**

Professional Experience

Persistent Systems Limited, Pune | DevOps Engineer

NOV. 2020 - PRESENT

- · Key responsibilities:
 - Writing **CICD** workflows for building and publishing the container images, binaries
 - Automated the manual container certification, Preflight tool testing procedure using GitHub Actions, Travis CI
 - Building multi-architecture images using GitHub Actions/CirclCI/Tekton and buildah
 - Using **Terraform** for automating infrastructure provisioning
 - Containerizing applications using Docker/Buildah and ensuring successful deployment on Kubernetes cluster
 - Setup K8s cluster in HA with **Kubeadm** on ppc64le architecture
 - Worked on **Ansible** playbooks, **Bash** scripts to automate the manual tasks
 - Ported open-source softwares to support IBM ppc64le Operator Certification, Container certification, ArgoCD,
 kubelogin, Gomplate, KCP, Dex, Pipeline as Code, Syft, ec-cli
 - Maintainer of various images, binaries for IBM ppc64le

Anubhooti Solutions, Pune | Flask Web Development Intern

DEC. 2018 - FEB. 2019

- · Key responsibilities:
 - Developed framework for Speech to Text application using Flask
 - Maintained user accounting details using SQLAIchemy

Education

BE, Computer Engineering, Pune University

PVG's College of Engineering and Technology, Pune August 2016 to October 2020

HSC, Maharashtra State Board

VPASC College, Baramati, Pune June 2015 to March 2016